Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Norton, Frank E. (Folder 263, Box 2)
  - Nourse, Edwin G. (Folder 264, Box 2)
  - Novotny, Frances (Folder 265, Box 2)
  - Nutter, Warren G. (Folder 266, Box 2)
  - Nystrom, Paul H. (Folder 267, Box 2)
  - N- Various Trade Associations, Exchange 1930 (Folder 268, Box 2)
  - N- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 269, Box 2)
  - N- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 270, Box 2)
  - N- Miscellaneous 1932-39 (Folder 271, Box 2)
  - O'Brien, Frank (Folder 272, Box 2)
  - Oklahoma State University Library (Folder 273, Box 2)
  - Olds, Irving S. (Folder 274, Box 2)
  - O'Leary, Paul M. (Folder 275, Box 2)
  - Oliver, Henry (Folder 276, Box 2)
  - Olsen, Herluf (Folder 277, Box 2)
  - O'Mahoney, Joseph C. (Folder 278, Box 2)
  - Oppenheimen, Robert (Folder 279, Box 2)
  - Orchard, C.R. (Folder 280, Box 2)
  - Owen, Robert L. (Folder 281, Box 2)
  - O- Miscellaneous 1920-47 (Folder 282, Box 2)
  - Pace, Norma (Folder 283, Box 2)
  - Payne, Wilson F. (Folder 284, Box 2)
  - Peaslee, Horace (Folder 285, Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airlines (Folder 286, Box 2)
  - Persons, Warren M. (Folder 287, Box 2)
  - Pigou, Arthur C. (Folder 288, Box 2)
  - Pierce, Edward J. (Folder 289, Box 2)
  - Pierson, John H.G. (Folder 290, Box 2)
  - Platzker, James (Folder 291, Box 2)
  - Political Science Quarterly (Folder 292, Box 2)
  - Pollard, Charles P. (Folder 293, Box 2)
  - Pollak Foundation (Folder 294, Box 2)
  - Polner, Walter (Folder 295, Box 2)
  - Poole, Kenyon E. (Folder 296, Box 2)
  - Pope, Loren (Folder 297, Box 2)
  - Potter, Alden A. (Folder 298, Box 2)
  - Potter, E.L. (Folder 299, Box 2)
  - Powell, O.S. (Folder 300, Box 2)
  - Power, John H. (Folder 301, Box 2)
  - Prather, Charles H. (Folder 302, Box 2)
  - Presbyterian University and Foreign Missions (Folder 1, Box 3)
  - Price, H.B. (Folder 2, Box 3)
  - Princeton University Library- Collins, D. (Folder 3, Box 3)
  - Princeton University Press (Folder 4, Box 3)
  - P- MIscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 5, Box 3)
  - P- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 6, Box 3)
  - P- Miscellaneous 1932-55 (Folder 7, Box 3)
  - The Quarterly Journal of Economics (Folder 8, Box 3)
  - Rand McNally and Co. (Folder 9, Box 3)
  - Ratner, Sidney (Folder 10, Box 3)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen (Folder 11, Box 3)
  - Reagan, Micheal D. (Folder 12, Box 3)
  - Redmond, W. (Folder 13, Box 3)
  - Reed, Philip D. (Folder 14, Box 3)
  - Regan, A.C. (Folder 15, Box 3)
  - Reierson, Roy L. (Folder 16, Box 3)
  - Reuss, Frederick G. (Folder 17, Box 3)
  - The Review of Economics and Statistics (Folder 18, Box 3)
  - Rice, Emmett J. (Folder 19, Box 3)
  - Rice, Morgan H. (Folder 20, Box 3)
  - Rice, Stuart A. (Folder 21, Box 3)
  - Richards, C.B. (Folder 22, Box 3)
  - Riddle, J.H. (Folder 23, Box 3)
  - Riefler, Winfield (Folder 24, Box 3)
  - Rinfret, Pierre A. (Folder 25, Box 3)
  - Ritter, Lawrence (Folder 26, Box 3)
  - Robertson, Willis A. (Folder 27, Box 3)
  - Robertson, J.L. (Folder 28, Box 3)
  - Robertson, Ross (Folder 29, Box 3)
  - Robinson, B.W. (Folder 30, Box 3)
  - The Robinson Foundation Inc. (Folder 31, Box 3)
  - Robinson, Roland (Folder 32, Box 3)
  - Rockeffeller, Nelson A. (Folder 33, Box 3)
  - Rodgers, Leo (Folder 34, Box 3)
  - Rodgers, Raymond (Folder 35, Box 3)
  - Roland Press Co. (Folder 36, Box 3)
  - Rolph, Earl R. (Folder 37, Box 3)
  - Rolph, Earl R. (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - Ronk, Sally S. (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Roos, Charles F. (Folder 40, Box 3)
  - Rosee, Kenneth D. (Folder 41, Box 3)
  - Root, Herbert W. (Folder 42, Box 3)
  - Rosenberg, Nathan (Folder 43, Box 3)
  - Ross, Emerson (Folder 44, Box 3)
  - Ross, M.O. (Folder 45, Box 3)
  - Rothbard, Murray (Folder 46, Box 3)
  - The Royal Bank of Canada (Folder 47, Box 3)
  - R- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 48, Box 3)
  - R- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 49, Box 3)
  - R- Miscellaneous 1932-43 (Folder 50, Box 3)
  - Sachs, William S. (Folder 51, Box 3)
  - Sakurai, Kinichiro (Folder 52, Box 3)
  - Sapir, Michael (Folder 53, Box 3)
  - Sasuly, Max (Folder 54, Box 3)
  - The Saturday Evening Post (Folder 55, Box 3)
  - Sauerhaft, Sidney J. (Folder 56, Box 3)
  - Saulnier, R.J. (Folder 57, Box 3)
  - Scattersood, Margaret (Folder 58, Box 3)
  - Schmidt, Emerson P. (Folder 59, Box 3)
  - Schnapper, M.B. (Folder 60, Box 3)
  - Schneider, Samuel (Folder 61, Box 3)
  - Schultz, Theodore W. (Folder 62, Box 3)
  - Schumpeter, J.A. (Folder 63, Box 3)
  - Schur, Leon M. (Folder 64, Box 3)
  - Scott, Lra (Folder 65, Box 3)
  - Sellier, Francois (Folder 66, Box 3)
  - Seltzer, Lawrence H. (Folder 67, Box 3)
  - Shapiro, S. (Folder 68, Box 3)
  - Sharfman, I.F. (Folder 69, Box 3)
  - Shaw, Edward S. (Folder 70, Box 3)
  - Shaw, William H. (Folder 71, Box 3)
  - Shere, Louis (Folder 72, Box 3)
  - Sharrar, Lee M. (Folder 73, Box 3)
  - Shields, Murray (Folder 74, Box 3)
  - Shoup, Carl S. (Folder 75, Box 3)
  - Siegel, Irving H. (Folder 76, Box 3)
  - Sifton, Paul (Folder 77, Box 3)
  - Simmons, Edward C. (Folder 78, Box 3)
  - Simpson, William B. (Folder 80, Box 3)
  - Singer, Hans (Folder 81, Box 3)
  - Slichter, Sumner H. (Folder 82, Box 3)
  - Smith, Dan Throop (Folder 83, Box 3)
  - Smith, Frank (Folder 84, Box 3)
  - Smith, George C., Jr. (Folder 85, Box 3)
  - Smith, Hilda (Folder 86, Box 3)
  - Smith, Jewell B. (Secretary to Mr. Smead) (Folder 87, Box 3)
  - Smith, Abbot S. (Folder 88, Box 3)
  - Smith, Richard B. (Folder 89, Box 3)
  - Smith, Warren L. (Folder 90, Box 3)
  - Smithics, Arthur (Folder 91, Box 3)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Folder 92, Box 3)
  - Snavely, T.R. (Folder 93, Box 3)
  - Snyder, Carl (Folder 94, Box 3)
  - Social Research - Strauss, Leo (Folder 95, Box 3)
  - Somers, Harold M. (Folder 96, Box 3)
  - Sonne, Christian H. (Folder 97, Box 3)
  - Speagle, Richard E. (Folder 98, Box 3)
  - Spengler, Joseph J. (Folder 99, Box 3)
  - Sprinkel, Beryl (Folder 100, Box 3)
  - Sproul, Allan (Folder 101, Box 3)
  - Stapp, Peyton (Folder 102, Box 3)
  - State, U.S. Department (Folder 103, Box 3)
  - Stein, Jerome L. (Folder 104, Box 3)
  - Stein and Roe (Folder 105, Box 3)
  - Stern, Earnest H. (Folder 106, Box 3)
  - Stevens, Dell H. (Folder 107, Box 3)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Folder 108, Box 3)
  - Stigler, George (Folder 109, Box 3)
  - Stine, O.C. (Folder 110, Box 3)
  - Stocking, George W. (Folder 111, Box 3)
  - Strachey, John (Folder 112, Box 3)
  - Strauss, William V. (Folder 113, Box 3)
  - Stricker, Adam K., Jr. (Folder 114, Box 3)
  - Surrey, Stanley (Folder 115, Box 3)
  - Sweet, Donald H. (Folder 116, Box 3)
  - Sweezy, Alan R. (Folder 117, Box 3)
  - Swanson, Ernest (Folder 118, Box 3)
  - Szymczak, M.S. (Folder 119, Box 3)
  - S- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 120, Box 3)
  - S- Miscellaneous (Folder 121, Box 3)
  - S- Miscellaneous 1932-55 (Folder 122, Box 3)
  - Tabatoni, Pierre (Folder 123, Box 3)
  - Taggart, Joseph H. (Folder 124, Box 3)
  - Tarnowsky, Ivan (Folder 125, Box 3)
  - Taylor, Amos E. (Folder 126, Box 3)
  - Temple, Alan H. (Folder 127, Box 3)
  - Tonenbaum, Henry (Folder 128, Box 3)
  - Terborgh, George (Folder 129, Box 3)
  - Tew, Brian (Folder 130, Box 3)
  - Thomas, Woodlief (Folder 131, Box 3)
  - Thompson, Charles D. (Folder 132, Box 3)
  - Thompson, Donald S. (Folder 133, Box 3)
  - Thomsen, F.L. (Folder 134, Box 3)
  - Thorp, Willard (Folder 135, Box 3)
  - Time Incorporated (Folder 136, Box 3)
  - Tinbergen, J. (Folder 137, Box 3)
  - Tintner, Gerhard (Folder 138, Box 3)
  - Tolley, George S. (Folder 139, Box 3)
  - Tolley, H.R. (Folder 140, Box 3)
  - Tostlebe, Alvin S. (Folder 141, Box 3)
  - Townsend, Walter (Folder 142, Box 3)
  - Treasury Department (Folder 143, Box 3)
  - Trefftzs, Kenneth L. (Folder 144, Box 3)
  - Tress, R.C. (Folder 145, Box 3)
  - Troxel, Emery C. (Folder 146, Box 3)
  - Tsiang, S.C. (Folder 147, Box 3)
  - Tucker, A.J. (Folder 148, Box 3)
  - Tucker, Rufus S. (Folder 149, Box 3)
  - 20th Century Fund (Folder 150, Box 3)
  - Tyndall, Gordon D. (Folder 151, Box 3)
  - T- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 152, Box 3)
  - T- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 153, Box 3)
  - T- Miscellaneous 1932-47 (Folder 154, Box 3)
  - Ullman, William (Folder 155, Box 3)
  - United Nations (Folder 156, Box 3)
  - U.S. Book Exchange (Folder 157, Box 3)
  - U.S. Congressmen (Folder 158, Box 3)
  - University of California (Folder 159, Box 3)
  - University of Chicago Press (Folder 160a, Box 3)
  - University of Chicago- Round Table and Industrial Relations Center (Folder 160b, Box 3)
  - U.S. Senators (Folder 161, Box 3)
  - University Microfilm (Folder 162, Box 3)
  - Upgren, Arthur (Folder 163, Box 3)
  - Upson, Brant (Folder 164, Box 3)
  - U- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 165, Box 3)
  - Vandon Press (Folder 166, Box 3)
  - de Vegh, Pell (Folder 167, Box 3)
  - Vickery, William McCall (Folder 168, Box 3)
  - Villard, Henry H. (Folder 169, Box 3)
  - Viner, Jacob (Folder 170, Box 3)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review (Folder 171, Box 3)
  - Von Szeliski, Victor (Folder 172, Box 3)
  - Voohris, Jerry (Folder 173, Box 3)
  - V- Miscellaneous (Folder 174, Box 3)
  - V- Miscellaneous 1932-41 (Folder 175, Box 3)
  - Wagner, Valentine F. (Folder 176, Box 3)
  - Waite, Warren C. (Folder 177, Box 3)
  - Wald, Haskell P. (Folder 178, Box 3)
  - Wall, Norman J. (Folder 179, Box 3)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Folder 180, Box 3)
  - Waller, James M. (Folder 181, Box 3)
  - Walsh, Correa M. (Regarding) (Folder 182, Box 3)
  - Wall Street Journal (Folder 183, Box 3)
  - Walsh, Henry G. (Folder 184, Box 3)
  - Wardwell, Charles A.R. (Folder 185, Box 3)
  - Warne, Colston E. (Folder 186, Box 3)
  - Washington, Virginia and Maryland Coach Company (Folder 187, Box 3)
  - Watson, Donald S. (Folder 188, Box 3)
  - Waugh, Frederick V. (Folder 189, Box 3)
  - Weiler, E.T. (Folder 190, Box 3)
  - Weinfeld, William (Folder 191, Box 3)
  - Weissman, Rudolph L. (Folder 192, Box 3)
  - Weisz, Eugen (Folder 193, Box 3)
  - Weitzman, Ellis (Folder 194, Box 3)
  - Weld, W.E. (Folder 195, Box 3)
  - Wernette, Philip (Folder 196, Box 3)
  - Westerfield, Ray B. (Folder 197, Box 3)
  - Weston, J.F. (Folder 198, Box 3)
  - Wetereau, James O. (Folder 199, Box 3)
  - Wheeler, John F.G. (Folder 200, Box 3)
  - White, H.D. (Folder 201, Box 3)
  - White, Melvin I. (Folder 202, Box 3)
  - Whittlesey, C.R. (Folder 203, Box 3)
  - Wicheman, Arthur A. (Folder 204, Box 3)
  - Wickens, Aryness Joy (Folder 205, Box 3)
  - Wilkes, M.R. (Folder 206, Box 3)
  - Williams, Faith (Folder 207, Box 3)
  - Williams, John H. (Folder 208, Box 3)
  - Willis, Brooke J. (Folder 209, Box 3)
  - Wilson, J.Y.S. (Folder 210, Box 3)
  - Wisconsion Tax Commission (Folder 211, Box 3)
  - Withers, William (Folder 212, Box 3)
  - Witherspoon, William (Folder 213, Box 3)
  - Wolcott, Jesse P. (Folder 214, Box 3)
  - Wolfe, A.B. (Folder 215, Box 3)
  - Wolozin, Harold (Folder 216, Box 3)
  - Wood, Ransey (Folder 217, Box 3)
  - Woodhoues, Chase Going (Folder 218, Box 3)
  - Woodward, Donald B. (Folder 219, Box 3)
  - Woodward, R.D. (Folder 220, Box 3)
  - Division of Statistics- Work Projects Administration (Folder 221, Box 3)
  - Wright, C. Ashley (Folder 222, Box 3)
  - W- Miscellaneous 1920-25 (Folder 223, Box 3)
  - W- Miscellaneous 1926-31 (Folder 224, Box 3)
  - W- Miscellaneous 1932-55 (Folder 225, Box 3)
  - The Yale Review (Folder 226, Box 3)
  - Yale University Press (Folder 227, Box 3)
  - Yasui, Takama (Folder 228, Box 3)
  - Young, Charles E. (Folder 229, Box 3)
  - Young, Ralph A. (Folder 230, Box 3)
  - Youngman, Anna (Folder 231, Box 3)
  - Y- Miscellaneous (Folder 232, Box 3)
  - Zaglits, Oscar (Folder 233, Box 3)
  - Abelson, Milton (Folder 1, Box 4)
  - Academy of Political Science (Folder 2, Box 4)
  - Achenstein, Asher (Folder 3, Box 4)
  - AFL-CIO Director of Research (Folder 4, Box 4)
  - Alexis, Marcus (Folder 5, Box 4)
  - Allsbrook, Ogden O. (Folder 6, Box 4)
  - American Bankers Association (Folder 7, Box 4)
  - American Economic Association (Folder 8, Box 4)
  - American Economic Review (Folder 9, Box 4)
  - American Finance Association (Folder 10, Box 4)
  - American Men of Science (Folder 11, Box 4)
  - Anderson, Leonall C. (Folder 12, Box 4)
  - Anderson, Paul (Folder 13, Box 4)
  - Applied Financial Economics Center (Folder 14, Box 4)
  - D'Anista, Jane (Folder 15, Box 4)
  - Aschheim, Joseph (Folder 16, Box 4)
  - Ashley, Thomas Ludlow (Folder 17, Box 4)
  - Atlanta Economic Review (Georgia State College) (Folder 18, Box 4)
  - Atlantic Economic Journal and Society (Folder 19, Box 4)
  - Atlee, John S. (Folder 20, Box 4)
  - Atwood, Edward C. (Folder 21, Box 4)
  - Backer Library - Harvard University (Folder 22, Box 4)
  - Housing Urban Affairs Commentary (U.S. Senate) (Folder 23, Box 4)
  - Banyai, Richard A. (Folder 24, Box 4)
  - Bean, Louis H. (Folder 25, Box 4)
  - Benston, George J. (Folder 26, Box 4)
  - Bissell, Richard M. (Folder 27, Box 4)
  - Black, Robert P. (Folder 28, Box 4)
  - Blackburn, Ben B. (Folder 29, Box 4)
  - Bordes, C. (Folder 30, Box 4)
  - Brademas, John (Folder 31, Box 4)
  - Bradford, Charles H. (Folder 32, Box 4)
  - Brandt, Harry (Folder 33, Box 4)
  - Brannon, Yerald M. (Folder 34, Box 4)
  - Braunmuller, Rae Jean (Folder 35, Box 4)
  - Brickman, Myrtle (Folder 36, Box 4)
  - Bridges, Sadler (Folder 37, Box 4)
  - Brill, Daniel H. (Folder 38, Box 4)
  - Brunner, Karl (Folder 39, Box 4)
  - Bubeck, C.H. (Folder 40, Box 4)
  - Bucher, Jeffrey M. (Folder 41, Box 4)
  - Burger, Albert E. (Folder 42, Box 4)
  - Burns, Arthur F. (Folder 43, Box 4)
  - Burstein, M.L. (Folder 44, Box 4)
  - Business Week (Folder 45, Box 4)
  - Cagan, Phillip (Folder 46, Box 4)
  - Campbell, Colin D. (Folder 47, Box 4)
  - Cargill, Thomas F. (Folder 48, Box 4)
  - Carlson, Keith M. (Folder 49, Box 4)
  - Carpenter, Keith (Folder 50, Box 4)
  - Carson, Carol S. (Folder 51, Box 4)
  - Carter, Anne P. (Folder 52, Box 4)
  - Chase, Sam (Folder 53, Box 4)
  - Christ, Carl (Folder 54, Box 4)
  - Cochran, James L. (Industrialism and Warburton's India paper of 1920s) (Folder 55, Box 4)
  - Cole, Don Preston (Folder 56, Box 4)
  - Coleberd, Robert E. (Folder 57, Box 4)
  - Columbia University Council for Research in Social Sciences (Folder 58, Box 4)
  - Columbia University Press (Folder 59, Box 4)
  - Commercial and Financial Chronicle (Folder 60, Box 4)
  - Conference on Research in Income and Wealth (Folder 61, Box 4)
  - Conlan, John B. (Folder 62, Box 4)
  - Contemporary Authors- Gale Research (Folder 63, Box 4)
  - Cosmos Club (Folder 64, Box 4)
  - Cramer, Edison H. (Folder 65, Box 4)
  - Crane, Philip M. (Folder 66, Box 4)
  - Daly, Donald J. (Folder 67, Box 4)
  - D'Arista Jane (Folder 68, Box 4)
  - Davis, Richard G. (Folder 69, Box 4)
  - Dewald, William G. (Folder 70, Box 4)
  - Dictionary of International Biography (Folder 71, Box 4)
  - Duncan, Joseph W. (Folder 72, Box 4)
  - Eastburn, David P. (Folder 73, Box 4)
  - Econometrica (Folder 74, Box 4)
  - Economic History Association (Folder 75, Box 4)
  - Economic Inquiry (Folder 76, Box 4)
  - The Economist (Folder 77, Box 4)
  - Edwards, Daniel J. (Folder 78, Box 4)
  - Eichengreen, Barry J. (Folder 79, Box 4)
  - Egan, Jack (Folder 80, Box 4)
  - Fabricant, Solomon (Folder 81, Box 4)
  - Fand, David I. (Folder 82, Box 4)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (Folder 83, Box 4)
  - Federal Reserve Banks (Folder 84, Box 4)
  - Federal Reserve Board and Federal Reserve Board of Governors (Folder 85, Box 4)
  - Fellner, William (Folder 86, Box 4)
  - Fels, Rendigs (Folder 87, Box 4)
  - Fenstermaker, Van J. (Folder 88, Box 4)
  - Fetter, Frank W. (Folder 89, Box 4)
  - Fisher, Joseph L. (Folder 90, Box 4)
  - Francis, Darryl R. (Folder 91, Box 4)
  - Frazer, William J. (Folder 92, Box 4)
  - Friedman, Milton (Folder 93, Box 4)
  - Gaines, Tilford (Folder 94, Box 4)
  - Galbreath, Kenneth (Folder 95, Box 4)
  - Garvy, George (Folder 96, Box 4)
  - George Mason College (Folder 97, Box 4)
  - Gilbert, Abby L. (Folder 98, Box 4)
  - Gilbert, Garry (FDIC) (Folder 99, Box 4)
  - Girton, Lance (Folder 100, Box 4)
  - Goldsmith, Raymond W. (Folder 101, Box 4)
  - Carter Golembe Associates (Folder 102, Box 4)
  - Goodman, Howard S. (Folder 103, Box 4)
  - Gorman, John A. (Folder 104, Box 4)
  - Gramley, Lyle E. (Folder 105, Box 4)
  - Graves, Mary (Folder 106, Box 4)
  - Grenfield, Robert L. (Folder 107, Box 4)
  - Grohs, Roy J. (Folder 108, Box 4)
  - Guise, Tom (Folder 109, Box 4)
  - Gurley, John (Folder 110, Box 4)
  - Guttentag, Jack M. (Folder 111, Box 4)
  - Gottfried, Haberler (Folder 112, Box 4)
  - Hansen, Bent (Folder 113, Box 4)
  - Harris, Lowell C. (Folder 114, Box 4)
  - Hart, Albert G. (Folder 115, Box 4)
  - Hasson, Joseph A. (Folder 116, Box 4)
  - Hegeland, Hago (Folder 117, Box 4)
  - Heller, Walter W. (Folder 118, Box 4)
  - Hencke, Paul (Folder 119, Box 4)
  - Hendershot, Ralph (Folder 120, Box 4)
  - Hobbs, Larry G. (Folder 121, Box 4)
  - Von Hoffman, Nicholas (Folder 122, Box 4)
  - Horsefield, Keith J. (Folder 123, Box 4)
  - Horton, Joseph (Folder 124, Box 4)
  - Hubbe, Jurgen (Folder 125, Box 4)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Folder 126, Box 4)
  - Humphrey, Thomas M. (Folder 127, Box 4)
  - Hunt, Lucy H. (Folder 128, Box 4)
  - International Platform Association (Folder 129, Box 4)
  - International Review of the History of Banking (Folder 130, Box 4)
  - James, Emile (Folder 131, Box 4)
  - Johns Hopkins Press 1966 (Folder 132, Box 4)
  - Johns Hopkins Press- Introduction to Volume (Folder 133, Box 4)
  - Johnson, Bruce A. (Folder 134, Box 4)
  - Johnson, Ivan C. (Folder 135, Box 4)
  - Johnson, Thomas F. (Folder 136, Box 4)
  - Jones, Donald W. (Folder 137, Box 4)
  - Jones, Homer (Folder 138, Box 4)
  - Jorden, Jerry L. (Folder 139, Box 4)
  - Journal of Finance (Folder 140, Box 4)
  - Journal of Political Economy (Folder 141, Box 4)
  - Journal of Money, Credit and Banking (Folder 142, Box 4)
  - Judd, John P. (Folder 143, Box 4)
  - Karmin, Monreo (Folder 144, Box 4)
  - Karnosky, Denis S. (Folder 145, Box 4)
  - Kaufman, George C. (Folder 146, Box 4)
  - Kelly, William A. (Folder 147, Box 4)
  - Kilpatrick, Robert W. (Folder 148, Box 4)
  - Kendrick, John (Folder 149, Box 4)
  - Kimbrel, Monreo (Folder 150, Box 4)
  - Klein, Benjamin (Folder 151, Box 4)
  - Klein, Lawrence R. (Folder 152, Box 4)
  - Koretz, Sidney (Folder 153, Box 4)
  - Kreps, Juantia M. (Folder 154, Box 4)
  - Laffer, Arthur B. (Folder 155, Box 4)
  - Landers, Ann (Folder 156, Box 4)
  - Latane, Henry A. (Folder 157, Box 4)
  - Lindaeur, John M. (Folder 158, Box 4)
  - Lombra, Raymond E. (Folder 159, Box 4)
  - Lothian, James R. (Folder 160, Box 4)
  - Luttrell, Clifton B. (Folder 161, Box 4)
  - Macesich, George (Folder 1, Box 5)
  - Macgregor, Donald (Folder 2, Box 5)
  - Machinery and Allied Products Institute (Folder 3, Box 5)
  - Marquis (Folder 4, Box 5)
  - Mason, Will (Folder 5, Box 5)
  - Mayer, Thomas (Folder 6, Box 5)
  - Mayne, Lucille S. (Folder 7, Box 5)
  - Mayo, Robert P. (Folder 8, Box 5)
  - McCracken, Paul W. (Folder 9, Box 5)
  - McEvoy, Raymond H. (Folder 10, Box 5)
  - McCouldrick, Paul F. (Folder 11, Box 5)
  - Means, Gardiner C. (Folder 12, Box 5)
  - Meiselman, David I. (Folder 13, Box 5)
  - Meltzer, Allan H. (Folder 14, Box 5)
  - Mercurio (Folder 15, Box 5)
  - Meyer, Paul A. (Folder 16, Box 5)
  - Mills, Frederick C. (Folder 17, Box 5)
  - Minsky, Herman P. (Folder 18, Box 5)
  - Mitchell, George W. (Folder 19, Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Parren J. (Folder 20, Box 5)
  - Mittra, Sid (Folder 21, Box 5)
  - Modigliani, Franco (Folder 22, Box 5)
  - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Folder 23, Box 5)
  - Mondale, Walter F. (Folder 24, Box 5)
  - Moore, Geoffrey H. (Folder 25, Box 5)
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company (Folder 26, Box 5)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research (Folder 27, Box 5)
  - National Economists Club (Folder 28, Box 5)
  - National Economic Research Institute (Folder 29, Box 5)
  - National Journal (Folder 30, Box 5)
  - Neal, Stephen N. (Folder 31, Box 5)
  - Okun, Arthur M. (Folder 32, Box 5)
  - Otey, Elizabeth (Folder 33, Box 5)
  - Park, Chan Moon (Folder 34, Box 5)
  - Partee, Charles J. (Folder 35, Box 5)
  - Patinkin, Don (Folder 36, Box 5)
  - Patman, Wright (Folder 37, Box 5)
  - Phelps, Edmund S. (Folder 38, Box 5)
  - Philbrook, Clarence E. (Folder 39, Box 5)
  - Phillips, Samuel H. (Folder 40, Box 5)
  - Pilgrim, John D. (Folder 41, Box 5)
  - Poole, Kenyon E. (Folder 42, Box 5)
  - Popkin, Joel (Folder 43, Box 5)
  - Prestopino, Chris J. (Folder 44, Box 5)
  - Proxmire, William (Folder 45, Box 5)
  - Rayney, Terry (Folder 46, Box 5)
  - Redlick, Fritz (Folder 47, Box 5)
  - Reuss, Henry S. (Folder 48, Box 5)
  - Rivlin, Alice - Correspondence w/ (Folder 49, Box 5)
  - Rostow, W.W. (Folder 50, Box 5)
  - Rowen, Robert (Folder 51, Box 5)
  - Ryan, Thomas G. (Folder 52, Box 5)
  - St. James Press- Writers Victory (Folder 53, Box 5)
  - Samuelson, Paul A. (Folder 54, Box 5)
  - Schmidt, Wilson (Folder 55, Box 5)
  - Schotta, Charles (Folder 56, Box 5)
  - Schultze, Charles L. (Folder 57, Box 5)
  - Schwartz, Anna Jacobson (Folder 58, Box 5)
  - Segal, Harvey H. (Folder 59, Box 5)
  - Selden, Richard (Folder 60, Box 5)
  - Seidman, William L. (Folder 61, Box 5)
  - Shafer, Joseph E. (Folder 62, Box 5)
  - Sharpe, Wihelmina (Folder 63, Box 5)
  - Shelton, William (Folder 64, Box 5)
  - Sherrill, William W. (Folder 65, Box 5)
  - Simons, Howard -Washington Post (Folder 66, Box 5)
  - Smithsonian Magazine (Folder 67, Box 5)
  - Snavely, William P. (Folder 68, Box 5)
  - Social Science Research Council (Folder 69, Box 5)
  - Solomon, Elinor (Folder 70, Box 5)
  - Solow, Robert M. (Folder 71, Box 5)
  - Solterer, Joseph (Folder 72, Box 5)
  - Southern Economic Association (Folder 73, Box 5)
  - Southern Economic Association Meetings, November 1978 (Folder 74, Box 5)
  - Southern Economic Journal (Folder 75, Box 5)
  - Southern Finance Association (Folder 76, Box 5)
  - Southern Journal of Business (Folder 77, Box 5)
  - Sparkman, John (Folder 78, Box 5)
  - Spencer, Roger W. (Folder 79, Box 5)
  - Sprinkel, Beryl W. (Folder 80, Box 5)
  - Strout, Dick (Folder 81, Box 5)
  - Sunley, Emil (Folder 82, Box 5)
  - Taylor, Charles T. (Folder 83, Box 5)
  - Templeton, William H. (Folder 84, Box 5)
  - Thomas, Brinkey (Folder 85, Box 5)
  - Timberlake, Hichard H. (Folder 86, Box 5)
  - Tobin, James (Folder 86a, Box 5)
  - Tower, John (Folder 86b, Box 5)
  - Trescott, Paul B. (Folder 87, Box 5)
  - Tuchman, Jill (Folder 88, Box 5)
  - U.S. Congressmen (Folder 89, Box 5)
  - University of California (Folder 90, Box 5)
  - Vatter, Harold G. (Folder 91, Box 5)
  - Vedder, Richard K. (Folder 92, Box 5)
  - Vernon, Jack R. (Folder 93, Box 5)
  - Wacht, Richard F. (Folder 94, Box 5)
  - Wallich, Henry C. (Folder 95, Box 5)
  - Ward, Richard (Folder 96, Box 5)
  - Waud, Roger N. (Folder 97, Box 5)
  - Weidenbaum, Murry (Folder 98, Box 5)
  - Weigel, Gerald E. (Folder 99, Box 5)
  - Weintraub, Robert E. (Folder 100, Box 5)
  - Western Economic Journal (Folder 101, Box 5)
  - Wetzel, James N. (Folder 102, Box 5)
  - Wetzler, Jim (Folder 103, Box 5)
  - Wilcox, James A. (Folder 104, Box 5)
  - Williams, Harrison A. Jr. (Folder 105, Box 5)
  - Woodworth, J. (Folder 106, Box 5)
  - Yeager, F.W. (Folder 107, Box 5)
  - Yeager, Leland (Folder 108, Box 5)
  - Yeats, Alexander J. (Folder 109, Box 5)
  - Yohe, William P. (Folder 110, Box 5)
  - Zinner, Paul (Folder 111, Box 5)
  - Lists of Articles by Clark Warburton (Folder 1, Box 6)
  - Lists of articles and to whom reprints were sent (Folder 2, Box 6)
  - List of Miscellaneous Articles and Memoranda(See Index Page) (Folder 3, Box 6)
  - Articles by Clark Warburton 1958-63 (Folder 4, Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Memoranda by Clark Warburton 1930-57 (1) (Folder 5, Box 6)